Hello friends welcome to
your own YouTube channel Jhala here we were
talking about wishing so
before doing so please
subscribe to our channel
and click on the bell button so
that you can get notified of upcoming videos
Kar do
[Praise] [Music] Kar do
[Music]
Jhala's [
Praise] [Music] Kar do [Music] Kar do [Music] Kar do [Music]
Send a message Kar do [
Music] Kar do [Music] to Ajay Ajay Ajay [Music] Kar do [
Music]
that a
Ajay Kar do [Praise] [Music] Kar
do [
Music]
[Praise] [
Kar do
Ajay
[Praise] Show more
Look at today's chart of numbers from here,
show us in the free market only, there might be
pressure here, so we have
some lines on the technical face, which you can
see in the village, so what we did is
some shots and  We marked the resistance level
like 09:15, it is going to go down, so
I also came to know in the market but this was to
create panic, so we had gone
below the level here,
subscribe there, leaving this means this is what
remains, so subscribe 108 10
minutes target-25,
it did a back to back and
touched the line from getting line which we had below it, so
our targets were achieved,
but when it was doing well, what would we have done,
if we kept
trailing, when we
looked at the free market, when we are ready to put 10 points in the
current account, this gives 10 points, that
means this was the pet less, but we will
see the development here, so what would we have done,
when it fell down, we kept loving our surplus, so
as soon as it
cracked in it,
as soon as it reached the support line of our line, it was almost
fitting like 0.5 price from the close, so
we subscribe to the laptop which we had placed here,
now we had met from here also, so
all the market  You can get more than double the target you set for yourself.
You just have to pay attention to the technical aspects
that will be shown on the chart.
You have to bring your own quintals. If
you follow Chakli on this issue, you can
get good results. By doing this, we
can see that we have made profit on almost all the things. So, on
this site, you will
see the withdrawal of 150% of our investment. If you want to see the profit in more, you have to
subscribe, then you don't have to do anything. If
you haven't subscribed to our channel yet, then
why not? The local market is sloping quickly, but still
we have got the trade. It is known that if
you follow the search,
Vindhyachal profit was visible here at the current rate. I
run it next to it,
but we do not add it in an hour. So
after that, see, the market remained the same the whole day.
I consolidated. So, more than just watching, you have to pay
more attention to medical colleges
and you will not be
able to earn much profit. So, I just wanted to share this with you in the market, so to
get such updates
For this please subscribe to our channel,
like and share it. Thank you, thanks for
watching Hai
Jhal.